nitro-pak.com 2002-06-03

# Inside Nitro-Pak: Our Stance on Your Privacy

**Nitro-Pak's Stance on Your Privacy**

* * *

This privacy statement shows our stance on protecting your information. Below is explained the following:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site.
  * The organization collecting the information.
  * How the information is used.
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Nitro-Pak’s control.
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact the site webmaster at [webmaster@nitro-pak.com](mailto:webmaster@nitro-pak.com).

**Information Collection and Use**  
Nitro-Pak is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Nitro-Pak collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Registration**  
In order to use the shopping capabilities of this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as badge or other identification number), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site.

**Orders**  
We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. This information is used strictly for our internal use and will never be sold to or shared with third parties.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Cookies are used on this website to track users browsing habits and add to some browsing enhancements such as auto login. No personably identifiable information is stored in the cookie. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the personalized experience will be somewhat hindered.

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We also use log files to track every action that every user makes while on this website. This is to enhance the error reporting capabilities so that we can ensure a secure, and error free shopping/browsing experience for the user. These log files are made available only to this sites coordinators and administrators.

**Sharing**  
No personally identifiable information obtained on this website, or in our business, is shared with any third party. We process all shipments and credit card authorizations internally. We do use an address verification system to ensure accurate package delivery. Your name and financial information is not used in this process.

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Nitro-Pak is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. The user must “opt-in” to receiving this publication. If the user wishes to unsubscribe from the newsletter, they may do so at the following link: [https://www.nitro-pak.com/editaccount.asp?section=1&action=edit](https://nitro-pak.com/editaccount.asp?section=1&action=edit). The user’s information supplied here will not be rented or sold to any other party.

**Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Tell-A-Friend**  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. Nitro-Pak will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Nitro-Pak stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact Nitro-Pak at [to be determined] to request the removal of this information from their database.

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘surfing’. To learn more about SSL, follow this link [http://www.nitro-pak.com/ssl](http://nitro-pak.com/ssl). Another online security precaution that we have employed is a firewall. Our web and email servers, as well as the rest of our network, reside behind multiple firewalls which act as barriers to unauthorized persons (hackers). This measure ensures that your information will not leave our hands.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, in an access-controlled room. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [security@nitro-pak.com](mailto:security@nitro-pak.com).

**Special Offers**  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

**Site and Service Updates**  
We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:**  
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct or update that user’s personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the [member information page](https://nitro-pak.com/myaccount.asp) or by emailing our Customer Support ([customers@nitro-pak.com](mailto:%20customers@nitro-pak.com)). However, once a user has placed an order with us, we will be unable to remove their information from our system.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our [customer information page](https://nitro-pak.com/editaccount.asp?section=1&action=edit) has an ‘opt-out’ mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don’t want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may opt-out of receiving these communications by visiting [https://www.nitro-pak.com/editaccount.asp?section=1&action=edit](https://nitro-pak.com/editaccount.asp?section=1&action=edit) and selecting the “unsubscribe” option.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
